

- Bogotá
- tom.pujalte@gmail.com
- +57 322 7079680
- https://tompujalte.com/
- i⇔ French
- Open to remote work
- Driving license

#### **Assets**

- Ability to identify needs and determine best course of action based on specifications provided by client or project manager;
- Prioritisation of communication with back-end developers, managers and designers to ensure information exchange in the application;
- Use of best practices to structure HTML, CSS and Javascript;
- Use of frameworks like React to build powerful and modular applications;
- Rigorous operation of tests to verify application is running smoothly and correct code when necessary;
- Provision of website technical support and technical and functional website
  - **documentation** for the customer.
- Ability to meet web development project deadlines, prioritise tasks based on their importance and manage time effectively

## Languages

#### French

Native

#### **English**

Fluent

#### **Spanish**

Limited working proficiency

#### **Interests**

#### Street photography

#### Music

Drums and guitar

#### Social networks

(a) @pujaltetom

in @tom-pujalte

# Tom Pujalte

## Web developer

Passionate web developer with one year of experience, I am looking for challenging projects that will allow me to continue to develop and push the limits of my technical skills. I have a PVT visa that allows me to work in Colombia. Available now.

## Work experience

#### App Developer - JavaScript React

From April 2022 to June 2023 OpenClassrooms Paris

- Realisation of 14 projects/websites, including: sports statistics dashboard (with graphs), accommodation reservation site, integration of banking API
- Professional simulations of real world client requests

#### Logistics Specialist

From January 2021 to December 2021 Librairie Kléber Strasbourg

- Reception of dozens of boxes of books every day
- Stock management and delivery to booksellers

#### Trainee Journalist

From December 2019 to February 2020

Radio Caraïbes International Fort-de-France

- Drafting, recording and editing of radio reports, including use of Audacity
- Research and information gathering, including the realisation of more than 50 interviews

#### Trainee Journalist

From October 2018 to February 2019 La Dépêche du Midi Toulouse

- Drafting of web articles and print media for the Toulouse area
- Capture of illustration photos to accompany articles

#### **Education**

#### App Developpement - Javascript React (RNCP35976)

From April 2022 to June 2023 OpenClassrooms Paris

- Coding websites in Javascript, HTML, CSS
- Training in React, Sass, MongoDB
- Code management with Git and GitHub

#### Multimedia Journalism

From September 2017 to June Institut Supérieur de Journalisme de Toulouse (ISJT) 2020 Toulouse

- Training in web, print, radio and TV journalism
- Main subjects: English, Orthography, Geopolitics, Ethics and Media Law

#### Master in Cosmos, Fields and Particles (first year)

From September 2015 to June 2017 Faculté des Sciences Montpellier, Toulouse

• <u>Main subjects:</u> Astrophysics, Cosmology and Particle Physics

### Bachelor of Science in Physics and Chemistry

From September 2011 to June 2014 Université de Nîmes Nîmes

 <u>Main subjects:</u> Fluid Mechanics, Organic Chemistry, Applied Mathematics, Quantum Physics

#### **Computer skills**

#### **Programming languages**

- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS

## Frameworks/Librairies

- React
- Chart.js, Redux, Sass